HEATHER CAMPBELL

heathe

heather.campbell1212@gmail.com

C

(270) 585-0754

0

Jamestown, KY 42629

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Goal-oriented Junior Web Developer and seasoned Sales Executive brings strong commitment to collaboration and solutions-oriented problem-solving. Use various web design packages to develop custom-crafted, customer-focused websites and designs. Committed to high standards of customer satisfaction, user experience, and usability. Lends detailed knowledge of customer relations to increase visibility.

SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- SASS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- Chrome Dev Tools
- React
- Git
- Terminal
- Web development projects
- Programming
- Microsoft Office
- Relationship-Building
- Teamwork
- Excellent work ethic
- Verbal and written communication
- Planning and Coordination
- Service Agreements
- Sales Closing
- Customer Relations
- Sales expertise
- Account development

LINKS

- https://www.linkedin.com/in/heather-campbell-b45b6515/
- http://www.bcskills.org/

WORK HISTORY

ERA Real Solutions - Real Estate Agent

West Chester, OH 05/2016 - 04/2017

- Managed contracts, negotiations and all aspects of sales to finalize purchases and exceed customer expectations.
- Generated leads for sales through cold calls and referrals.

LCS - Sales Executive

Loveland, OH 07/2005 - 06/2015

- Increased revenue by implementing effective sales strategies in all aspects of sales cycle process from prospecting leads through close.
- Managed entire sales cycle across customer accounts, proposing and closing sales to achieve total revenue growth, profit and customer satisfaction plans.
- Presented products to clients using dynamic presentations and practical use-case scenarios.

EDUCATION

BCSkills Academy

Glasgow, KY

Web Development

 Coursework in HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Chrome Dev Tools, React, Git and Terminal.

W.W.Grainger - Government Account Manager

Dayton, OH • 03/2002 - 06/2004

- Analyzed past sales data and team performance to develop realistic quarterly sales goals.
- Directed work of efficient administrative team maintaining accurate sales, inventory and order documentation.
- Executed local, regional and national marketing and branding initiatives to drive sales within existing and prospective accounts.